lumberliquidators.com 2017-09-17

# Privacy & Security | Lumber Liquidators

## Privacy & Security

Effective: February 5, 2009  
Last Updated: January 11, 2016

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The following Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for Lumber Liquidators retail stores, call center and websites, including LumberLiquidators.com (collectively, the "Sites"). By visiting our stores or the Sites, contacting us by telephone or otherwise interacting with us, you consent to the information practices described in this policy.

We respect your right to privacy and through this policy seek to explain, among other things, our practices regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information. To assist you with understanding our processes, policies and practices, we have provided answers to questions that you may find most important:

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS COLLECT?**

We collect personal information such as your contact information (e.g., name, phone number, e-mail address), billing/shipping information (e.g., credit card number, shipping or home address), and/or your personal preferences (e.g., product wish-lists, hobbies, likes and dislikes relating to the products we may sell). When submitting personal information on an online form, we will identify which fields are required in order to fulfill your request. Additionally, our Web server automatically collects click-stream information such as the address (or "URL") of the website that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you have entered on our site.

**WHEN DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS COLLECT THE INFORMATION?**

While shopping or taking advantage of services available at Lumber Liquidators retail stores, businesses, call centers or visiting the Sites, we may ask that you provide certain information about yourself. For example, we request personal information when you set up an account online, purchase products or services, schedule delivery or installation, join a frequent buyer program, participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey, contact Lumber Liquidators with a question or concern, submit a review, apply for employment with Lumber Liquidators, or participate in other activities. In addition, when using our Sites, our servers may collect click-stream information as described above. Lumber Liquidators may also use third party providers of customer information to improve the accuracy of our customer database, to increase our understanding of our customers or to identify potential customers.

**HOW DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS USE THE INFORMATION?**

We use the information you provide in order to 1) fulfill and process requests for products, services or information, 2) administer shopping or reward club accounts, 3) provide customer services, 4) administer sweepstakes or promotions, 5) offer new products and services, 6) measure and improve the effectiveness of our Sites, our marketing endeavors or our services and offers, 7) tailor our online or in-store offerings to your preferences, 8) administer surveys, 9) send marketing communications from us or third parties in which we feel you may be interested in, (10) protect against and prevent fraud and unauthorized transactions, (11) comply with and enforce industry standards and/or legal requirements, (12) alert you about product issues, or (13) other business purposes.

**DO THE LUMBER LIQUIDATORS SITES USE COOKIES, OTHER TECHNOLOGIES OR THIRD PARTIES TO INDIRECTLY COLLECT INFORMATION?**

**Cookies and other Technologies**  
A cookie is a small data file that a website may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your hard drive. Our Sites use cookies to simulate a continuous connection - cookies let us "remember" information about your preferences and session, and allow you to move within areas of our Sites without reintroducing yourself.

Our Web server automatically collects the address of the website that you came from before visiting our Sites, which browser you used to view our Sites and any search terms you have entered on our Sites.

Our Sites may also use other technologies to track which pages on our Sites our visitors view. This data helps us understand how visitors use our Sites.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how you may prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies or how to disable cookies altogether. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or receive a promotion tailored to you. However, Lumber Liquidators is not responsible for and does not guarantee the effectiveness of browser tools.

We or our service providers may also use Flash cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash or similar technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded or installed by you on your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, and personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help visitors to our Sites to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our Sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. They may be recognized by other sites or by our marketing or business partners. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser may not remove Flash cookies. Click here to learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable.

For more information on your options with respect to how your information is used and how you can opt out from receiving advertising, see below: Do I Have Choice Regarding How My Information Is Used?

**Third Party Service Providers**

Our Sites may use third party service providers to serve ads, send e-mails and analyze website traffic on our behalf. These companies may use technologies similar to those outlined above to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails. They may also use information about your visits to our Sites and other websites so that we can provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers information about your site navigation and purchases.

**Do Not Track**

Do Not Track ("DNT") is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. Currently, our Sites do not respond to DNT mechanisms.

**DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS SHARE THE INFORMATION I'VE PROVIDED?**

We may share personal information with third parties in limited circumstances. For example, we may release personal information to third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: fulfilling our customers' orders, sending Lumber Liquidators marketing communications on our behalf, delivering packages, scheduling and performing installations, servicing products, fulfilling subscription services, conducting research or surveys, sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Lumber Liquidators, or processing credit card payments.

Lumber Liquidators' companies are affiliated entities and wholly owned subsidiaries of Lumber Liquidators, Inc. As such, any information you may provide to us either online or offline may be combined or shared between current or future Lumber Liquidators entities, affiliates and subsidiaries.

From time to time, we may be required to provide personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. Further, we may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

We may release personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

In addition, the information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please see your choices in the section below.

**DO I HAVE CHOICES REGARDING HOW MY INFORMATION IS USED?**

If your information is currently being used to send you marketing communications, you can opt-out at any time. All marketing e-mail and direct mail communications from Lumber Liquidators, such as hot deals or special offers, tell you how to stop receiving them.

To opt-out of receiving marketing communications from Lumber Liquidators:

Follow directions on a marketing e-mail or direct mail communication from us; Call 1-800-366-4204; Send an e-mail with your current contact information to [customercare@lumberliquidators.com](mailto:customercare@lumberliquidators.com); or Send a request with your current contact information to:  
Lumber Liquidators  
Attn: Marketing Privacy Manager **3000 John Deere Rd.  
Toano, VA 23168 ******

To opt-out of receiving marketing communications from third-party marketers:

Follow directions on a marketing e-mail or direct mail communication; Call 1-800-366-4204; Send an e-mail with your current contact information to [optout@lumberliquidators.com](mailto:optout@lumberliquidators.com); or Send a request with your current contact information to:  
Lumber Liquidators  
Attn: Marketing Privacy Manager  
3000 John Deere Rd.  
Toano, VA 23168 

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and e-mail address and indicate specifically what type of marketing communications you wish to stop receiving. This will ensure we identify you correctly in our systems and accurately process your opt-out request.

Lumber Liquidators will take the appropriate steps to implement your request to opt-out. Please note that due to production and mailing timelines, it may take up to ten (10) business days for e-mails and up to six (6) weeks for direct mail to make the requested change. Until that change takes effect, you may still receive marketing communications from us.

Also, please note that you may still receive business-related communications such as order confirmations, product recall information or other administrative communications.

**HOW CAN I UPDATE OR CHANGE MY INFORMATION?**

Lumber Liquidators wants your information and preferences to be accurate and complete. We provide several different methods for you to update or change the information you give us.

To update or change your information:

If you've created an account on LumberLiquidators.com, you can update your information after logging into your account; Call: 1-800-366-4204; Send a request to [CustomerCare@LumberLiquidators.com](mailto:CustomerCare@LumberLiquidators.com); or Send a request to:  
Lumber Liquidators  
Attn: Customer Care  
3000 John Deere Road  
Toano, Virginia 23168 

**HOW DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS SECURE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Whether you are shopping online, by phone or at a Lumber Liquidators retail store, we have industry standard security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access and alteration of the information under our control. Such measures include administrative, technical and physical protections and safeguards.

Safe Shopping Policy

Because your credit card security is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that your payment information is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The Lumber Liquidators Sites use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL"), to protect your credit card information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number. In-store Web stations operate over a private, secure network.

**Choosing a Personal Password**

When you create an online account on the Sites, you need to select a personal password that you will remember. It must be at least six (6) characters. To maximize your level of protection, you should choose a "strong" password that includes a combination of all of letters, numbers, or symbols. We urge you to keep your password safe; you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any other account information.

Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we take reasonable precautions to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. Lumber Liquidators cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail and you do so at your own risk.

**ARE LINKS TO OTHER SITES ON THE LUMBER LIQUIDATORS WEBSITES COVERED BY THIS POLICY?**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites that may be accessible through the Sites. Our Sites contain links to other sites operated by third parties, including but not limited to third party sites that display Lumber Liquidators' trademarks. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other sites to learn how they collect and use information about you.

**DOES LUMBER LIQUIDATORS COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

The Sites are not directed at children and we do not seek or intend to collect information from children who are under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you should not provide personal information to us on the Sites or otherwise. If we learn that a minor has submitted personal information to us, we will take all reasonable measure to delete such information from our databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except as necessary to protect the safety of a child or as otherwise required or permitted by law). If you become aware that a minor has submitted personal information to us, please contact us.

**IS THERE CERTAIN INFORMATION THAT CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS CAN REQUEST RELATING TO LUMBER LIQUIDATORS' USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. An individual may make one such request per year. To make such a request, please contact us as follows:

By e-mail at customercare@lumberliquidators.com; or By mail at:  
Lumber Liquidators  
Attn: Marketing Privacy Manager  
3000 John Deere Rd.  
Toano, VA 23168  

**DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY GET UPDATED?**

This Privacy Policy may be updated and revised from time to time without notice, and we will post the updated policy on Sites with the effective date of the change. You agree that the information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may contact you with notices concerning our Privacy Policy, but you should check the Sites periodically to review any changes.

**IS THERE A WAY TO CONTACT LUMBER LIQUIDATORS WITH QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you can do the following:

Call 1-800-366-4204; Send an e-mail to customercare@lumberliquidators.com; or Send a letter to:  
Lumber Liquidators  
Attn: Marketing Privacy Manager  
3000 John Deere Rd.  
Toano, VA 23168
